s3browser.com 2010-02-16

# NetSDK Software - Privacy Policy - Software Development Company. TntDrive, S3 Browser, Handy CD Ripper.

## Privacy Policy

 **Information Collection and Use**   
Unless the user provides it voluntarily, NetSDK Software does not collect any personally identifiable information about visitors of the website. Some pages permit visitors to request additional information. Visitors are able to e-mail messages to NetSDK Software that will contain the user's name and e-mail address, as well as any additional information the user may wish to include in the message. NetSDK Software uses the information visitors provide about themselves to fulfill those visitors' requests. E-mail addresses are used to answer messages received only. 

**Information Collected During Purchase**   
When you place an order online with us, we use a third-party e-commerce service. We do not keep credit card information as part of your product registration. We keep information about purchasers of our products in database (name, email address, mailing address, phone...) to fulfill purchaser request only (lost program, keys...). Our products are listed at http://www.netsdk.com. NetSDK Software may use purchaser information to send free upgrades (including new registration information), information about our new products and services. We will not sell, share, or rent purchaser information to third parties. 

**Log Files**   
We use IP addresses and we track navigation path to analyze trends and administer the site. IP addresses and URLs are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links**   
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that NetSDK Software is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by NetSDK Software website.

 **Security**   
Given the nature of the Internet and the fact that no security system is perfect, NetSDK Software cannot promise that the information you provide will never be obtained by unauthorized persons. NetSDK Software does, however, utilize industry-standard practices to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration and destruction. Such measures include using firewalls and security layers to protect certain sensitive transmissions of information. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**   
NetSDK Software reserves the right to change our privacy policy from time to time.
